["Judgement Day" playing]
[narrator] Previously...
Did you tell him we only had a friendship?
-No.
-He made it seem like you told him again.
...on Love Island USA...
I don't care about your feelings.
Why do you keep making shit happen?
...the villa...
Bro. don't come heated. yelling at me.
This is bullshit. I'm over it.
...clashed.
Fucking douchebag.
I don't trust you.
I don't want to see you around me.
-Fuck.
-Don't fuck with Bergie.
No. I don't give a fuck.
There was a dangerous liaison...
I couldn't get you
out of my head if I tried.
Aw. really?
I just feel betrayed by two people.
and two people that I really trust.
...and America's vote...
"Those with the fewest votes
risk being dumped tonight."
...piled on the pressure.
[message alert]
"Anna and Leonardo. Hannah and Marco.
you were not included in the vote."
-[message alert]
-"Will all other Islanders please stand?
"The first couple saved by the public is
Kay Kay and Keenan."
"Destiny and Harrison."
"Kassy and Bergie."
"Carmen and Victor.
only one of you will leave
the villa tonight."
"Who goes and who stays will be decided
by your fellow Islanders."
Fuck.
-I'd like to vote Victor.
-I'm gonna go with Victor.
-I'm just voting for Carmen.
-I'm voting for Carmen. too.
-I'd like to vote for Carmen.
-I choose Carmen.
-I'mma go Victor.
-Gonna go with Victor.
-I'm gonna vote Carmen.
-Victor.
Five-five.
I'd rather go all in on Carmen.
Does anybody wanna
support him in that decision?
Oh. my God.
It's a hard decision.
[theme song playing]
["Won't Save You" playing]
♪ Would you keep it a secret ♪
♪ If I tell you that you're dreaming ♪
[narrator] Welcome to Love Island USA.
America has decided that Carmen and Victor
are the least compatible
couple in the villa.
Now. the Islanders face a choice.
Do they save the tough. fearless fighter
who takes no BS from anyone.
or do they save Victor?
The Islander that we decided to choose...
["Won't Save You" music playing]
...came down to a lot of different factors.
Honestly. we were split.
There was on one end
someone who has displayed
that they want something serious
and long-term outside of here.
And then on another shoe.
there was someone
who does have a potential match here.
So. we came down
to which one of those we should honor.
♪ Oh. no ♪
♪ I won't save you
If I'm being honest. babe ♪
♪ Put the fear in you ♪
♪ It's a crooked truth ♪
♪ But you lied to me
Just cause you wanted to ♪
♪ Oh. no ♪
♪ I won't save you if I'm being honest... ♪
So. the Islander...
that we're choosing to keep in the villa...
is...
Carmen.
["Losing you" playing]
[softly] I'm so sorry.
♪ The shadow fades ♪
♪ You're walking away ♪
♪ A hundred steps I'm wasting away ♪
♪ On my heart ♪
[Victor] I would like to say that if...
I would have never changed anything. uh.
that I have done here.
Everything that you have seen
has been. like. truly who I am.
with my best choices...
and my worst. also.
I'm gonna miss you all.
-We'll miss you. too. Victor. Well said.
-Yeah. definitely. Well said.
♪ Falling down ♪
♪ 'Cause I lost you ♪
♪ That heart. nobody can take ♪
Thank you. brother.
Good luck in everything.
I just wanna say
I'm gonna learn from that mistake.
-You can learn whatever you want.
-[chuckles] I'm trying.
Yeah. You have a lot of things to learn.
-All right.
-Just be careful.
I will.
I just want you to know I'm the person
who swapped my vote in your favor.
[Carmen] Thank you.
And it was honestly because
Bergie saw a connection with you.
-I love you.
-I love you. too.
-Thank you.
-Girl. of course.
I'm just feeling guilty.
I don't think I have any right
to be here over him.
You also have this just sense of
it being my fault. you know?
Like. when I got here. like.
he was my strongest connection.
and I did steal him. and what if I hadn't?
You know? So. it's just... I feel...
I feel bad.
And to me. that's why I was like.
"Man. I fucking love my dawg."
"I love my dawg so much. bro."
I'm beyond blessed. you know. to have met.
like I said. one of the truest men.
Amen to that.
I'm definitely gonna miss Victor.
I believe he deserved to be here.
I think that he deserves to find love.
I think he deserved another chance.
We already have said
everything over there.
But you know. you have me.
like. inside. outside.
Uh...
-We love you.
-[all cheering]
♪ It's not like we can get one more try ♪
♪ To a story that we can't rewrite ♪
I have kinda mixed emotions.
but I don't have any regrets.
I haven't met the love of my life here.
It's somewhere out there.
and I have to keep looking.
We'll see what's next.
♪ Losing you ♪
[narrator] Poor Victor's suffered
every wrestler's worst nightmare.
He's been slam-dumped.
and some of the boys aren't too happy.
[Keenan] I'm just fucking disgusted.
Ooh. I gotta catch my tongue.
'cause I might start saying some shit.
[Marco] Carmen didn't deserve it.
I think it was a petty save.
Victor was definitely more deserving.
So. I pray to God
she doesn't embarrass Bergie.
He was too solid to go. bro.
Bro. he shouldn't have been up there
in that fucking position.
All right. Bro. honestly...
[Keenan sighs]
...we all know who should have been
in that fucking position. bro.
I voted for Victor for a certain reason.
He is not somebody that...
He didn't come here to fuck around.
-Literally. bro.
-And that's what kills me.
You know what I mean?
And that's why my original vote
was for Victor.
And it's just. like. the reason
why I'm so pissed is because it's like...
Bergie don't even know if...
"I'm taking a fucking risk."
And he's like.
"Bro. if another dude comes in
and she goes ahead
and just ignores the fuck out of Berg.
now you took a fucking risk."
Like. you just...
There was no hard decision for him.
There wasn't no this. that. and third.
We literally gave him the opportunity.
[narrator] Carmen was saved
to give Bergie a chance with her.
and if Carmen's not married to Bergie
with three kids.
a picket fence. and a Labrador
before Casa Amor.
she'll have let everyone down.
So. no pressure.
But what's up?
What did you want to talk about?
I just want you to know. like.
Bergie is the one who
-got you in.
-Dude. no. I know. and I wanna die.
I just straight up asked Bergie.
I said. "Bergie. if Carmen's in here.
do you want to pursue a future with her
and risk that maybe Carmen might find
someone else who she's interested in."
And then he's like... he's like.
"I will risk it with Carmen."
-Can I confide in you real quick?
-Mm-hmm.
Here's the thing. It's like...
Ninety percent of my anger
was directed towards Victor.
but Bergie had ten. So it was like.
"I don't wanna talk to anyone."
So. the part that's upsetting me about...
with Bergie is. like.
"Let's go pull Victor.
Let's get to the bottom of this."
And he stops me halfway.
and grabs me and goes.
"Can I give you a compliment?"
And I said... Um...
And I'm. like. heated because
I'm about to go grab Victor. you know?
And I'm like. "Yeah." And he goes.
"You're such a strong woman."
And so it was just like...
The fact he knew he was kind of like
leading me into this conversation
and then made this "strong woman" comment
like I was gonna go fight this battle
was a bit like...
I don't know if I want a partner
that's gonna... instead of being direct.
he almost used Victor as an excuse.
He was like.
"Victor said you said it again."
I need a partner
that's willing to be upfront
and the way
that situation was handled is not...
what I would be looking for
from a partner.
[narrator] When Kassy and Leonardo
were on the balcony.
Detective Anna was conducting surveillance
from an old Chevy with a flask of coffee.
12 donuts. and a picture of her family
glued to the dashboard.
Hannah and I were sitting
down by the kitchen.
-and I had heard you bring up my name.
-Mm-hmm.
I say to Kassy.
"Why are you looking at me like that?"
"You know what you're doing."
Um. just little things like that
that are really disrespectful.
I deserve to know before this
because I've been nothing
but honest and open with you.
So it's very hurtful to hear someone...
Like. two people you really care about.
your couple-up
and one of your best friends...
talk about you
when you're sitting down below
and you're not involved
in the conversation.
-as well as having flirty banter.
-Yeah.
So that's. like.
I would never do that to you.
I would never do that to Kassy.
I felt embarrassed like shit
down there. you know?
Like. you should never
make someone feel like that.
Of course not.
Especially someone you're coupled up with.
So that's hurtful. you know.
I'm not here to clear up
what I've done wrong.
I'm just going to give you...
So. you can agree you guys were flirting?
-Yes.
-Yeah.
And that's not correct to me.
I'd rather tell you the truth than...
I'm not going to lie to your face
on my poor actions.
Well. I do appreciate you
telling the truth now.
but I would like to say that I'm no longer
interested in getting to know you.
-Mm-hmm.
-So I feel like that's all I have to say.
I understand what I was doing
was very disrespectful towards you.
and I understand you are done
with what we have.
and all I can do is apologize
for me making that mistake.
And I'm very sorry.
Everything was going so good
with you and I
that I thought I could just crush
and squat down my inner feelings
for Kassy. right?
-And it got to the point...
-But you never expressed that to me.
No. I know. because I didn't want it
to interfere with me
trying to get to know you to a deeper...
But. to me. that's bullshit.
so I'm just gonna
end the conversation there.
I apologize
and I won't take up more of your time.
["Deep End" playing]
♪ I don't wanna love you ♪
♪ I don't wanna hold you ♪
♪ I don't wanna show you how ♪
♪ You do all I need
And I went in the deep ♪
♪ And looking for some solid ground ♪
["FOMO" is playing]
♪ I could be in London
Starring at the Albert Bridge ♪
♪ I packed up a suitcase ♪
♪ And never pulled the trigger
On the trip ♪
I just want you to know.
I wanna talk to you.
but I know that
I'm gonna give you your space.
Maybe tomorrow or later.
I just know that
you need your time right now. so...
[Keenan] My thing is.
I'll always be accountable.
Did I fuck up? Pfft. Major.
-But you know it now.
-But I know it. right?
But I couldn't hide the feelings
that I still deep down had for her.
Because end of the day.
I just wish I was way more
respectful about it for Anna.
♪ Oh. and I don't know ♪
♪ What keeps me holding on to something ♪
♪ That I know is never gonna be right ♪
-Leo fucking tickled my toe.
-[laughing]
You can't speak Spanish anymore.
I mean. I can. just to the fucking mirror.
[in Spanish]
[Leonardo exhales sharply]
-Okay.
-Do you know what I mean?
Mm-hmm.
♪ I guess that
It's the fear of missing out ♪
♪ The wonderin' what we'd be doing now ♪
♪ If I was there holding your hand ♪
♪ And everything
Had gone the way we planned ♪
♪ I guess that I'm afraid of letting go ♪
♪ And knowing
That I'll never really know ♪
♪ What could have been
And that's the hardest part of it ♪
♪ If I'm honest
And I get down to the heart of it ♪
♪ I got a fear of missing out ♪
♪ Out on everything that
Could have been between the two of us ♪
♪ You and me
I got a fear of missing out ♪
♪ Out on something written in the stars
Or in your arms that was meant to be ♪
♪ I guess I got the fear of missing out ♪
♪ The wonderin' what we'd be doing now ♪
♪ I guess that I'm afraid of letting go ♪
♪ And knowing
That I'll never really know ♪
♪ What could have been
And that's the hardest part of it ♪
♪ If I'm honest
And I get down to the heart of it ♪
♪ I got a fear of missing out ♪
["Technicolour Dreams" playing]
[narrator] Welcome back to
Love Island USA.
After Victor left last night.
Kay Kay found it surprisingly hard.
At least I think that's what she said.
Her voice was a bit muffled
and she was strangely out of breath.
[snickering] Shit. I'm not in the mood.
Nobody wants to get up right now.
♪ It's only technicolour dreams ♪
Listen. you've dug yourself
a nice little hole.
I am fucking very aware to the obvious.
I freaking love you.
I think some new meat
will be in here today.
How does it feel to be Bergie?
Bergie keep coming through.
I keep making...
Just barely surviving. you know?
[both chuckle]
♪ 'Cause we could use the company ♪
♪ You decide what you believe ♪
♪ It's only technicolour dreams ♪
How do you feel about Leo's situation?
He can fuck off.
[narrator] There's something Bergie's
never experienced
which can be sweet. soft.
sometimes a bit flaky.
They come in all shapes and sizes
that can be enjoyed anytime of the day.
I'm talking. of course. about ladies...
Cereal. I said "cereal."
What are you eating?
[chuckles] Cereal for the first time ever.
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling pretty good. We'll see...
Me too.
...what today brings.
A lot of things went down last night.
Oh. my gosh. Yeah.
I was like. "You know what?
I'll risk it with Carmen."
There's not many opportunities
in the real world
where you feel that spark and you're like.
"Yeah. I'm willing
to go out on that spark."
I'm really proud that you spoke
and said what you wanted.
I know. And you were right there too.
And I was like. "Dang it."
No. I was proud of you
because everybody was like.
"Bergie. do this. do this."
Even if Carmen doesn't talk to me.
I took the risk.
But. yeah.
-we'll just have to wait and see.
-Yeah.
If Carmen left last night.
I would've never been able to find out
where we stood.
if there's a potential relationship there.
But I don't wanna put any pressure on her.
so I'm just gonna be open
to whatever happens.
I've been able to get deep with Kassy.
and she's been there for me.
and I'm not gonna just
turn my back on her. for sure.
Are you gonna try
to talk to Leo again or...
What's your plan there?
I didn't know if I was going to go home.
So. you had to get
that last conversation out.
Last convo. And he pretty much didn't know
if I was going to leave either.
He said he was gonna be honest.
and he said everything.
How he was feeling.
He can't help but see that me and him
could've been something strong.
It's the girls that are mad at me.
-And hey. let them be mad at me. right?
-At the end of the day...
It's like. I'm here for me.
-Yeah. Not here for Friend Island.
-Not Friend Island. So...
-We might go home. But you know what?
-What?
We're gonna go all out.
-Yeah. exactly. So...
-What the hell?
We can do what everybody wants us to do.
But we know that's not what we want.
-Yeah.
-So...
[groans]
[Kassy] In the beginning.
I was trying to respect the girls.
but at this point. I'm gonna do me.
And with Leo. it's not like he's just some
random guy that I haven't talked to.
I was coupled up with him
in the beginning.
I ended shit with him.
and we still gravitated
towards one another.
There's going to be people hating on us.
having eyes on us.
But so what?
So be it. I don't care at this point.
[narrator] Harrison likes Destiny.
but she's not as forward
as the girls he's used to.
Like all Australian men.
he wishes Destiny would show
a bit more interest
in what he's got going on down under.
I'm usually used to someone
that's. like. flirtatious.
Yeah.
I guess flirtatious and out there.
a little bit like Anna...
-[Leonardo] Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
-...and Jasmine was.
But I need the back mind that Destiny has.
You need the two in one.
-Yeah.
-'Cause I feel like I'm a bit like that.
I'll be cheeky. but I'm also not...
I'm. like. reserved.
And I feel the cheekiness
not coming out of me with Destiny.
-Uh-huh.
-And I think. it's just 'cause I'm...
I can see that she's starting to develop
a little bit of feelings and...
-Yeah.
I can see it's starting to... I just...
I think she wants a bit more.
wants it to keep going down that path.
But I think the mind-set
might be a little different.
-Yeah.
[Harrison] I feel like Destiny. she's
feeling more than what she's letting on.
And I don't want to lead her on.
And then... And then change things.
And so I'm just cautious
'cause I don't wanna hurt her.
I see exactly what you mean.
I want you to know that I see it.
And it's not leaving my mouth.
-I'd appreciate you keeping it quiet.
-Of course.
'Cause I just don't like
that sort of stuff...
-I got you.
-My man.
-Yes. sir.
-[both laugh]
[narrator] Hannah voted to save Carmen.
and she's regretting her decision.
We've all made decisions we regret.
For example. Marco's wishing
he'd gone for acrylics instead of gels.
I actually made the mistake on the save.
I could have saved Victor.
We could've saved Victor
'cause Carmen came in with you.
So. I could have definitely
got her to be like...
-That would've left...
-Then you would have lost Leo or...
No. It would've been Keenan and him.
then it would've been you and...
It would've had to be Bergie and them.
No way Bergie...
People are protective over Bergie.
I would hope so.
Right after it happened.
I talked to her trying to emphasize
how Bergie is the reason why she's here.
And then she was talking about
how that night
when everything went down
between Bergie. Victor. and them.
Bergie...
When they were walking over.
Bergie said something like. um.
"You're such a strong woman."
And it rubbed Carmen
the wrong way. I guess. [chuckles]
-[Hannah] She. I guess...
-I wanna go. "Hmm."
This is just actually insane.
[Hannah] I just don't like that.
It seems like she's looking for something
to be mad about. Like. huh?
He probably didn't even mean it like that.
[Marco] She's not interested in Bergie.
-[Hannah] Exactly.
-[Marco] That's what kills me.
God. I wish Victor was still here.
I was trying to get you to switch.
but you weren't picking up my mechanism.
I didn't know that. I thought that
she was still really feeling Bergie.
-[Hannah] I did.
-Be fucking for real.
You can't see through that?
Yeah. I love you. Hannah.
but you knew since day one. Shit.
Shit. Anna sees through it right away.
Why? Why is that...
Because I need a toenail clipper. guys.
-Who would have...
-Leo has some.
-Shit.
-He told me. He told me he has some.
I don't wanna use his toenail clippers.
That's the least you could do.
["Sugar Sweet Venom" playing]
I wish I just had
went about it a better way.
♪ You tried your best
Yeah I know you did ♪
-[Anna] Keenan.
-Uh-huh.
-Do you have toenail clippers?
-Yeah. I do.
-In my. uh. black little pouch.
-Thank you.
♪ Once you've tasted surrender ♪
♪ Sugar sweet venom ♪
♪ Made like heaven ♪
♪ Just for you ♪
Leo and Kassy
are eating breakfast together.
-No. they're not. Anna.
-Yeah.
[Anna] You learn things
about people in the villa.
and it's just very disappointing
how you can treat someone like that.
It's not the fact that
there is a connection there.
It's the fact that you're just being
a not-so-great person.
Kassy... That's not a real friend
right there.
And no girl should ever be with a man
that treats her like that.
So we're all good here.
♪ Sugar sweet venom ♪
♪ Just for you ♪
[narrator] Welcome back to
Love Island USA.
Keenan has a habit of singing words
that describe what he's doing.
It's lovely.
Although. I do have to
turn his microphone off
when he goes to the toilet.
[singing] Making pancakes.
Making pancakes.
How do you feel. though. girl? Girly girl.
I feel good.
In the beginning. I was really caring
about everyone's input.
the friendships and stuff.
Yeah. That's been kind
of fucked up with. you know. here.
Now. I'm just like. "I have to do me."
-"I have to choose me this time."
-Yeah. yeah.
So. look. bro. if you're having your
feelings. you're having your feelings.
but you... Like.
you gotta pull her for a chat first.
With the person you're gonna couple with.
You literally could've just been like.
"I'll talk to you. Give me one second."
In that time. you go pull Anna.
be like. "Look.
I'm having this. this and feelings."
Now that's justified.
Now nobody can look at anybody crazy.
but when you don't have
that conversation. then it looks messy.
-But...
-At the end of the day.
he's a grown-ass man and he made
the decision to have the conversation.
That's on Leo. That's on Leo.
I just realized I have one earring on.
-Yeah. I mean. he made the choice. like...
-Yeah.
That's his choice.
And he's gonna have to live with
whatever happens because of it.
How are you feeling. Miss Kay Kay?
-I'm feeling all right.
-Yeah.
Carmen still hasn't talked to Bergie.
That shit's so fucked.
And she was like. "Yeah. I get that."
But when all that drama was happening.
and she pulled all three of them.
I guess it turned her off
because Bergie and Carmen
were walking to go meet Victor
-so they could talk about everything.
-Mm-hmm.
So. they're walking
and then I guess Bergie stops her.
-He's like. "You're such a strong woman."
-"You're such a strong woman."
Okay. you know this.
And she's like.
"The fact that he wanted me to confront."
I don't take it as that.
I take it as Bergie was probably
just complimenting her.
But you know.
when you're not into somebody.
you kind of look for little...
That's how I'm taking it.
I'm taking she might be
looking for little things to...
-[sighs] You know what I mean?
-Yeah. I do know what you mean.
And that really fucking makes me mad.
[Kay Kay] Yeah.
We did. I'ma tell you why.
Yeah.
[Kay Kay] She's not interested in that.
The decision we made was based on that...
and I don't think
that that's gonna happen.
Ultimately. we decided to save Carmen
because of Bergie's statement.
This was the determining factor.
The one thing
that was different from Victor.
Why you're here... Because of Bergie.
[Kay Kay sighs]
I gotta hit the gym today.
I got winded walking up these stairs.
Destiny made me fire pancakes
and I just feel like a fatty right now.
-Oh. yeah. I need an hour to digest.
-[Anna] Yeah.
[Carmen] But just in general.
I love you all.
I'm glad I'm still here.
And I know that was hard on everyone.
but...
Thanks for all riding for me
and giving me my second chance.
-[Anna] Ride or die.
-I appreciate you guys.
-Ride or die. baby.
-Ride or die. Love you all.
I can't live without that avocado toast.
Shit.
I did not think I'd be playing cards
in Love Island.
I didn't think I'd be learning
how to play Clubs in Love Island.
[narrator] Hannah's made a burger
using Dairy Queen General Manager
Bergie's special recipe:
A bit cheesy with absolutely no sauce.
-Yeah.
-Okay. Want to go get Bergie?
Yeah. Let's go get the Bergster.
-[Hannah] Bergie?
-Yo. What's up?
-Go for a chat?
-Yeah. Come on.
Yeah. With me and Anna.
Forget us.
-We're gonna go upstairs.
-[Bergie] Let's go.
To the girls' room.
Do you have any idea
of what happened last night?
[Bergie] I have an idea.
Kassy's like.
"Yeah. Leo's still flirting with me.
so I wonder if there's something there."
She had an opportunity
to tell Bergie about it.
but not her own friends?
[Bergie] Yeah.
Fuck.
Yeah. so she's been thinking about
doing that for a while and then...
-Fuck.
-Yeah. I just don't know...
Yeah. Cause like. obviously.
I've been pursuing Carmen
and I've been open about that
the whole time.
[Anna] Yeah. As you should.
And like... Yeah. I just don't know.
[laughs]
-Has Carmen talked to you?
-No. she hasn't yet. so...
[Hannah] And you're all
over there playing cards.
[Bergie] Yeah.
I feel like we saved the wrong person.
if I'm being blunt with you.
Because I saved them for you.
And I don't wanna
put that on you to feel guilt.
but the fact that
she hasn't even talked to you...
-Yeah.
-But you're over there playing cards.
-[Anna] Yeah.
-What are you doing here?
She's been avoiding him.
Like. he would've been the first person
I talked to after the dumping.
He would've been the first person
I talked to this morning
if she was really interested in him.
She said the whole thing
that happened with you and Victor.
it showed that you aren't mature guys.
You know what I mean?
There's always a "but."
-And I feel like when you like someone...
-There's no "buts."
-...there's no "buts."
-You just know.
That's how she's been
the whole time with you here.
[Bergie] I was just hopeful. you know?
It just sucks.
["Final Teardrop" playing]
At the end of the day. you are too good
to have someone make you feel like this.
You need to respect yourself and say.
"You know what? This is what I deserve."
I know. I just want someone that wants me.
I shouldn't give up on it yet.
just from what the girls are saying to me.
I just want someone to be there for me
and. you know. meet me halfway.
♪ I just decided
Not to give this love no more ♪
[sighs] We got you. Bergie.
♪ This will be my final teardrop ♪
[narrator] Welcome back to
Love Island USA.
Anna has a couple of words
she wants to say to Kassy.
I'm gonna go out on a limb here
and guess that the second one is "off."
I will say that I want you to be happy.
and I want you to find your person.
What's surprising to me is
-I trusted you and...
-Yeah.
...when I was talking to Leo.
when you were in a couple with him.
I would tell you details that would
make me uncomfortable telling you
just because I wanted to be a good friend
and keep you in the loop
of what our relationship is like.
Yeah. Yeah. I do apologize for that.
I just... The reason why I didn't
was because I didn't know what it was.
I wanted to get that clarity.
So. why didn't you have
that conversation with me?
'Cause you know
I would've been happy about it.
You know that I joke around
about everything.
I didn't know how it was going to go.
But you should've had that experience...
That learning experience
from Kay Kay and Keenan.
I'm sorry that I didn't
communicate to you. I am sorry.
But either way. I would've looked
like the bad guy. Either way.
No. you wouldn't have.
["Victorious" playing]
I didn't know
what he was gonna fucking say.
That doesn't matter.
You still owed me a conversation first.
-Okay. well. that's what I'm doing now.
-It's too late.
I'm sorry. but I just thought
I might be going home.
I need to fucking talk to him
and see what this is.
I can't control what the fuck he said.
Like. honestly...
But you can control
how you act upon it before it.
Yeah. And from here on out.
I. a hundred percent. am listening.
and I'm gonna try and do that.
I really am.
[Anna] I don't care that her and Leo
are continuing their relationship.
It was a disrespectful blindside.
and you don't treat
your fellow Islanders like that.
Like. I want you to be happy.
and Leo could be your person.
But this is not something
I would continue as a friendship.
I'm glad that you're learning
from your mistakes 'cause...
Yeah.
-That's lovely.
-Yeah.
-But. Anna. I just want you to know like...
-It's okay.
-Thank you.
-We'll just end it.
I kind of knew what was gonna happen.
Uh... It was just suckier
than I'd expected.
I thought it was gonna be
with us hugging it out.
But instead. it was her thinking
I'm a piece of shit.
She's just playing the victim.
She would say. "I'm sorry. but..."
And. like. you can apologize.
but it doesn't mean anything
if you keep doing it.
Yeah. it doesn't.
It doesn't. It loses its meaning.
She pretty much was saying how
I should have learned from my mistakes.
I was basically telling her
I don't wanna be her friend.
but I was trying to word it properly.
Bro. I'm fucking disappointed. like...
-We live together.
-Yeah. It's...
Do you not care
how your actions affect other people?
I know I'm doing the right thing
because it's like...
This is what we're supposed to do.
Like. we're here to find love.
Like. this might be selfish.
but it's like...
People can say what they want.
As long as I'm with my person.
-like. I'm fine. you know?
-Mm-hmm.
♪ I'm an unstoppable force ♪
["So Dangerous" playing]
Oh. we stepping out tonight.
-How are things with you and Kassy going?
-Damn good.
-No shit.
-[Bergie snorts]
But still. you know.
you're in a full-blown couple.
And everybody thought
you and Anna was solid.
so that shit was a blindside.
That was a blindside to everybody.
People are mad that
Anna thought she was in a hundred percent.
and her friend
and her boy went off. That sucks.
Baby. we want you to feel
whatever you feel.
This is Love Island. baby.
Go whatever the romance...
But it's just ways. baby.
You could go about it a better way.
There's ways to it!
Kassy. y'all were eye-fucking.
[laughing]
♪ I'm dangerous. so dangerous ♪
Rocker girl.
An emo girl.
♪ ...dangerous. so dangerous ♪
♪ I don't fight ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't care ♪
♪ Dangerous. so dangerous ♪
All right. Islanders.
let's fuck it up tonight.
Cheers to that.
-Let's go.
-Cheers!
-Salud.
-Here's your shot. baby.
[song ends]
["Don't Check for Me" playing]
♪ Just wanted to love you ♪
♪ Didn't want nothing from you ♪
Everyone told me that
you really fought for me last night.
I did. You've been my number one
all the way through.
I got a second chance.
I saw you. I was like.
"No way this is happening right now."
Everything was just matching.
You want four kids. I want four kids.
You're Christian. You're from Wisconsin.
-We both love all four seasons.
-Yeah.
I haven't been able to find
any other Islander that shares that.
You just make me feel
like no other girl here.
I feel so bonded to you
for the exact same reasons.
And I feel that connection.
In that situation. between you and Victor.
I felt you kind of brought me into it.
-And then I had to fight that battle.
-Yeah.
It was something
that could've been dealt with without me.
I got kind of
thrown to the wolves a little bit.
["Hold On" playing]
I don't wanna waste my time.
I don't wanna waste your time.
We're in here to find our person.
and in here you just have to figure out
is it friendship or is it romantic?
It just made me realize.
that's gonna be my best friend in here.
[sighs]
This is where I struggle
in the real world.
I can always get a date with a girl.
I just can't get the spark
and pursue a romantic connection.
I always get into the friend zone.
Why does this keep happening?
♪ Stay strong ♪
♪ And don't you worry about the future ♪
♪ You can trust to never lose it ♪
I'm sorry. Are we okay. though?
Do you think we can
move forward as friends?
Because I cherish our connection so much.
You still do feel like home to me
in this place compared to everyone else.
-you know?
-Yeah. We can continue as friends.
Obviously. you know. I would like
to try to continue a relationship.
But if that's where you're at.
yeah. we can continue as friends for sure.
-I appreciate that. Bergie.
-Yeah.
You picture your future with this person.
like. the next 50 years.
You're putting stuff in your head.
and now it's just like... That's all gone.
It's just done.
I just want my person.
I think you're the most amazing person.
-All right?
-I hear it all the time.
-Because you are. Bergie.
-I know. but I just can't...
You hear it all the time because you are.
I know. but I just can't get
a relationship spark. That's what sucks.
No. you know what? It's coming.
And the next girl is fucking for you.
I hope so.
♪ Tell me everything's all right ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
[narrator] Welcome back to
Love Island USA.
Earlier. Anna gave Kassy
the cold shoulder.
Now. Kassy is giving herself
Pull your cardigan up.
You'll catch your death!
-What you feeling?
-I do wanna ask. like...
I know Anna is fully backed out.
If she was to stay.
would you try to get.
you know. both of us still?
No. no. no. no. no. no.
'Cause here's the truth of the matter.
Right now. I feel like
you're where I want to be.
-Mmm. Aw.
-And. like...
Well. we'll have to see. I guess.
We'll have to see. then.
How are you feeling. though. boo boo?
I feel good. I feel blessed.
I feel like the luckiest girl
in the world.
I'm really good with where we at.
I just like taking time
just to vibe with you.
chill with you. check in with you.
Yeah.
I miss you.
-You miss me?
-All the time.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
I let you have your fun.
-You did.
-Your mine's now.
-Oh. for real. boo boo?
-Yeah.
Let me get some kisses.
I probably got 16 kiss marks on my cheek.
-You don't.
-Okay. Damn.
What do you wanna do?
-What do you wanna do?
-I don't know. What do you wanna do?
-I know what I wanna do.
-You wanna kiss me.
Is that what you want?
Mm-hmm.
You want a little besito.
You do. I do.
So. what's happening?
So is this lust or is this real?
-This is real.
-You sure?
We haven't even done anything.
You is dangerous.
[both giggling]
No. no. no. no. no.
Oh. you're dangerous.
-No. I'm not.
-Yes. the fuck you are.
-Uh-uh.
-Uh-huh.
Uh-uh.
Oh. God. Get out of my head. yo.
You're blushing.
Okay. so...
This whole night.
Leo has not talked to me.
-Okay. not there.
-It's just me.
[Anna] She can hear.
Kassy and Leo have been talking all night.
I feel like
I just keep getting disrespected.
I don't know if I'm overreacting.
that's why I'm asking.
It's even happening so fast.
You're a couple.
Yeah. So. can you owe me the respect
for the time being.
and maybe not jump into it?
I genuinely think he doesn't think
you want to talk to him.
No. he doesn't.
But that's not what
the problem is. though.
It's the fact that they're. like...
He needs to mature. He needs to be a man.
and say. "You know what?
Maybe this is too soon."
-I get it. though. She's. like. emotional.
-As she should be.
-It's a lot to see that.
Fuck. I don't know.
No. I don't think Anna should pull them.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
Maybe you pull him
and be like. "I feel disrespected."
"We're still a couple.
Do you not think you owe me that respect?"
-Should I do that now?
-Yeah.
♪ The love you gave cuts deep inside ♪
♪ 'Cause all it is is beg ♪
♪ In disguise ♪
Had a good little night.
I'm definitely happy that. um. we chatted.
Mm-hmm.
I didn't wanna hold back. like.
so. I was like. you know...
Finally just say. "Fuck it. we ball."
and go for it.
[moans]
Where is Leo?
I'm actually gonna talk to him.
-Okay.
But I don't know where he is.
[Hannah] They just walked that way. Anna.
[sighs] Okay.
[Destiny] Do your thing. Anna.
And you better step.
You a bad bitch.
-Thank you.
-Of course.
-I'm happy.
-Are you?
Too bad we don't
share a bed right now. though.
But I still think you should talk to Anna.
Not the easiest...
Do you mind if I talk to you for a minute?
-It'll be quick.
-To me?
-Yeah.
-Here. I'll get up.
Thanks.
Um... Hello.
Hey.
So. I'll make this quick
because you're a busy guy.
I just want to say
I feel disrespected again.
Okay.
I know that's probably
not your intentions.
but we're still in a couple.
-Mm-hmm.
-Um...
You still owe me the respect
to just be a genuine person.
And the fact that you had talked to Kassy
pretty much like 40-50% of the day.
as well as stand next to her
when you get the text.
and then cook with her...
It's uncomfortable to watch.
Yeah.
Are my noodles ready?
I don't know
how much disrespect I can get.
I feel like...
I don't know what I did wrong.
This is so new.
You shouldn't be jumping into it
with her so quickly.
Or. at least. do it more privately.
Okay.
I wish you would have moved
with more respect.
I didn't mean to rub that into your face
because I didn't think. like...
It's not rubbing it into my face.
It hasn't even been 24 hours.
Like. you don't do that.
You know. this is not right.
I wouldn't do that to you.
And I. obviously. you know
I want you to find your person.
but you should find it without hurting
other people along the way.
-100%.
-And what you did today hurt me.
I didn't want to keep being disrespectful.
Just know that
I would never do that to you.
-I know.
-I have too much respect for you
to be embarrassing you
in front of a huge group of people.
Thank you for your time.
♪ Take the mask off your eyes ♪
[narrator] Welcome back to
Love Island USA.
Marco's written an autobiography
called What I'm Thinking.
but he won't let anyone near it.
I never let people read
what I'm thinking. [chuckles]
I feel like you're very caring.
I feel like
that's a very accurate assumption.
We're very physically attracted
to each other.
-Oh. I'm emotionally attracted too.
-Are you?
Oh. yeah.
What are you attracted to? Tell me.
I'm attracted to your positive manner.
-I try to be.
-You try to be. exactly.
[chuckles]
I'm attracted
to your demeanor as an individual.
How you let your presence be known.
It's good to be attracted
to someone physically.
Like. I like that.
I want someone to be attracted to me.
but I don't want it to be everything.
Yeah. I got you.
I like that you're listening.
and you're not just like.
"Yeah. whatever."
Mm-hmm.
Attention to detail.
I just feel like
I'm such a good girlfriend.
Oh. You got to be a good mother.
that's very important to me.
Yeah. definitely.
I'm definitely smitten with Marco.
which is just so gross.
He farts all the time.
and he kind of has a smart-ass mouth.
and it's just. like.
why the hell do I like him?
I always think with my head. not my heart.
but I feel like I'm just... Keep vibing.
And he keeps surprising me
because he just opens up.
He tells me random-ass stuff.
which makes me like him even more.
I don't freaking know. but I do.
so I'll just keep vibing with that.
Something's a-coming.
["Freak with You" playing]
[moans]
Oh. [chuckles]
I just punched this thing.
The light's gonna go out.
You're just horny.
No. I'm not.
It's just how you are.
This is comfortable.
[Kassy] I want a snack.
-That part. they're stressing that part.
-[phone chimes]
-Oh. shit.
-Shut the fuck up!
-It was you. it was you.
-It was me.
-It was me. it was me.
-It was you.
[gasps] I got a text!
-Oh. my God.
-Are you fucking kidding me?
I got a text.
Perfect timing.
[reading]
[all] Oh!
Kay Kay and Keenan!
[all cheering. laughing]
We gonna be on a date...
On a scale from one to ten.
how excited am I?
A hundred.
Whoo!
-Fellas!
-Hey. fellas.
Man. I'm buzzing right now.
I can't wait just to go ahead.
Go ahead!
That's it!
Do you have any lingerie?
-Fuck around and find out. bitch!
-Let's see the options.
Where the fuck them...
Where the fuck the gray sweats at?
-The gray sweats.
-That's all you need!
-Y'all know it.
-That's all you need.
Where the fuck is the gray sweats at?
Gray sweats and a beater. bro.
Y'all know what fucking time it is.
-Oh. that's sexy.
-[all cheers]
With the shawl.
I got the red lingerie picked out.
The girls helped me pick it out.
It's real sexy. Real statement.
Keenan loves me in red.
-[Carmen] I'm so excited.
-Same. Same. Same.
And you're just... Bro. not sleeping
in the same room as everyone.
Agh. I'm so excited.
I can hear you walking down them steps.
Yeah. I'm coming!
Oh. shit.
Oh. shit!
Now. you look fucking delicious.
-Thank you.
-You look so good.
[all cheering. laughing]
Good night. ladies and gentlemen.
-Have fun!
-Salutations.
I will see all you guys in the morning.
We love you!
Mmm. If I had to guess
what they were gonna do...
Make Love Island babies.
-After you. my lady.
-[screams]
-[all cheering] Bye!
-Have a good night.
[laughing]
Oh. no.
[narrator. echoing] Next time...
Things get steamy in the Hideaway.
And three new Islanders crash the villa.
My name is Jonah.
When I get into the villa.
I'm definitely gonna be
like a kid in a candy shop.
I might come out a diabetic.
My name's Emily.
When I see a guy that I'm interested in.
I'm definitely ready to piss
some people off to get what I want.
My name is Kenzo.
When I see something I want. I go for it.
So I don't care if she's coupled up.
I'm gonna shoot my shot.
I don't remember
the last shot I've missed.
♪ Nothing can stop me now ♪
♪ And you're never gonna get it
'Cause I'm the one wearing the crown ♪
[theme song playing]